It seems like there might also be a ton of other considerations if you're
听起来好像有很多东西需要考虑的
thinking about hearing impairment, visual impairment.
如果你还要涉及到听力缺陷、视力缺陷等
When people are designing for all these users can you compromise the design?
如果要为所有的用户进行设计 那会不会损害设计本身？
Will the product maybe change too much?
产品会不会发生太大的变化？
>> Yeah, it's a very good question and there definitely does
是的 这个问题很好
seem like there's a lot at first glance to really consider.
第一感觉好像是有很多东西需要考虑
And in actuality,
实际上
if you do leave all these considerations to the end of the product cycle,
如果你在产品周期的最后阶段才考虑这些问题
it can compromise the product because there's a lot of rethinking and
它会损害产品设计 因为你需要进行重新思考
refactoring that needs to go in, to just kind of fit these things in.
产品重构 才能放入这些元素
And so that's why we're always asking people, and informing,
所以我们一直告诉、教育大家
and educating people on how to think of these things early on.
尽早地考虑这些问题
I think when you just look at the general steps within the design process,
我认为你可以在设计阶段的一般步骤中
all of the points that when you're thinking about accessibility,
考虑无障碍功能的问题
they're integrated in every step that you're already thinking about.
这样就能在每个步骤中将它整合进去
So again, with color contrast,
我们再拿颜色对比度举例
you're already thinking about what is your color palette going to be.
你已经想好了调色板会是什么样子
So, then just on top of that you have some additional standards to maybe try
另外 你首先得试着满足一些其他标准
to follow and look at to ensure that there's enough contrast there.
并确保有足够的对比度
Hey, we're here at the OXO website.
这里是 OXO 的网站
I wanted to bring this up because I feel like they have a really good
我这里把它提出来 是因为我觉得
approach to universal design, and
这是实现通用设计的一个好方法
they have this great quote on here that I wanted to read.
他们的引言非常好 我这里读一读
When we talk about designing for accessibility or universal design,
当我们想要进行无障碍或者通用设计时
it's important to note that that does not mean designing products fully usable
必须谨记我们不是说要设计
by everybody,
所有人都能完全使用的设计产品
since there is no product that can truly fulfill the needs of all users.
因为没有产品能真正地满足所有用户的需求
But, when all users' needs are taken into consideration in the initial
但是 如果在初始设计过程中
design process,
就考虑了所有用户的需求
the result is a product that can be used by the broadest spectrum of users.
最后得到的产品能实现最广范围的用户
So, I feel like that's a great way to kind of sum up that, yes,
所以我觉得这是个很好的总结
there is a lot to consider, but it's not about making compromises.
是的 有很多需要考虑的东西 但这不意味着要损害设计本身
In the end, when you do consider these things up front,
如果你一开始就考虑了这些东西
you end up with a better product overall.
你最后能得到整体上更好的产品
>> Yeah, that's great.
是这样的 很棒
And how can an entrepreneur learn more about accessibility?
企业家们该如何学习更多的关于无障碍功能的内容呢？
What resources are available to them?
他们可以使用哪些资源？
>> The great thing is there's a lot of resources out there online.
现在很好的是 网上有很多资源
A few just to kind of rattle off,
我这里随便说几个
are the Web Content Accessibility Guidelines, which you can find online.
先是网站内容无障碍指南 你可以网上找到
That's a really thorough list of standards that you would want to meet,
这个是你想要且必须要满足的
and need to meet.
各种标准的详尽清单
And they have great examples on there as well, and resources.
里面还有很多很好的例子和资源
Different companies have provided their own design guidelines.
不同的公司也提供了他们自己的设计指南
Google is one of them, which you can see here.
Google 也是其中之一 你可以看到 在这里
This is the Google Accessibility website and specifically these are our design
这是 Google 无障碍网站 上面有我们的具体的设计指南
guidelines that we came up with, which are based on a lot of the standards
里面的很多标准
that were developed by the Web Content Accessibility Guidelines.
都是基于网站内容无障碍指南
Apple has a great resource as well, for their accessibility design guidelines.
苹果也有提供很好的资源 它们的无障碍设计指南
And there's also some really interesting tools out there.
网上还有很多非常有趣的工具
There's plugins.
有各种插件
There's a plugin called SEE that allows you to kind of simulate what your
有种叫 SEE 的插件能够模拟
page or site would look like with different vision impairments,
你的网页或网站在不同的视力缺陷和色盲用户
as well as color blindness.
的眼中是什么样子的
Yeah, so there's a lot that's out there.
是的 网上有很多的资源
>> Great.
非常棒